<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Douglas Minh-Duc Phung]]></title><description><![CDATA[Remember to breathe with Doug Phung]]></description><link>http://www.dougphung.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 08:07:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Responsible Growing]]></title><description><![CDATA[It takes courage to try something new, I used to inspire others to break their comfort zone, Ninety-nine problems, but I’m not alone, Put my…]]></description><link>http://www.dougphung.com/responsible-growing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.dougphung.com/responsible-growing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;It takes courage to try something new,&lt;br&gt;
I used to inspire others to break their comfort zone,&lt;br&gt;
Ninety-nine problems,&lt;br&gt;
but I’m not alone,&lt;br&gt;
Put my heart on the line, dance to the music,&lt;br&gt;
Now I’m becoming real again.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Mama said to take care of myself and help others in need,&lt;br&gt;
So put the excuses back on the shelf,&lt;br&gt;
and put one foot in front the other towards a new goal,&lt;br&gt;
Even the airlines say help yourself before the others.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dont be afraid of the unknown,&lt;br&gt;
Creating hope used to be my philosophy,&lt;br&gt;
A navy seal told me,&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;If you want to change the world,&lt;br&gt;
Swim with the sharks and make your bed regularly&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Now I’m stepping outside my comfort zone again.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Gravity exists because it’s afraid of letting go,&lt;br&gt;
but the natural state of man is to be free.&lt;br&gt;
So I believe it’s okay to push the status quo,&lt;br&gt;
But first, don’t forget to take care of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wasted Time]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why get out of bed? If you don’t make promises, You can’t break any.]]></description><link>http://www.dougphung.com/wasted-time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.dougphung.com/wasted-time/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 05:54:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Why get out of bed?&lt;br&gt;
If you don’t make promises,&lt;br&gt;
You can’t break any.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello 2020]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is my first post on my new blog. I bought this domain for 5 years. The Chinese aren’t stealing dougphung.com again for awhile! Oh woe…]]></description><link>http://www.dougphung.com/hello-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.dougphung.com/hello-2020/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 05:54:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on my new blog. I bought this domain for 5 years. The Chinese aren’t stealing dougphung.com again for awhile!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh woe. 2019 was exciting, with lots of ups and lots of downs.
I said good-bye to so many good friends back in DC, and I’ve made a few friends in LA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love wasn’t in the Californian air when I got here. And I experienced a lay-off / firing for the first time. But 2 weeks later I had a new job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January&lt;/strong&gt;-Went snowboarding with the bestest of friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February&lt;/strong&gt;-Submitted my two weeks notice to Capital One. Crystal moved to LA. I slept on an air mattress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March&lt;/strong&gt;-I had two final round interviews in California, but it didn’t work out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April&lt;/strong&gt;-I drove cross-country with my Dad across America. Visited some great friends along the way and saw family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May&lt;/strong&gt;-Got a job at a luxury real estate startup making a website engine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June&lt;/strong&gt;-Went bottom-fishing on a boat and caught the limit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July&lt;/strong&gt;-Sarah and friends were in town for Anime Expo. 7.4 earthquake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August&lt;/strong&gt;-Celebrated the release of v3 at work by parting at Kylie Jenner’s new house (the startup had the real estate agent’s keys), but I was let go the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September&lt;/strong&gt;-Started working at EnterMedicare, a medicare startup. Started learning more indepth about America’s healthcare environment. Got to visit home for a week before I started and played the first week of Fairfax Ultimate’s Fall League.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October&lt;/strong&gt;-James Lee came down. and Jtow came to visit and we drove down to see USAU club nationals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November&lt;/strong&gt;-Thanksgiving was spent with Cousins down in Long Beach. Shut down Wishpanda. Attended my first NBA game. Clippers vs Trailblazers @StapleCenter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;December&lt;/strong&gt;-Crystal and I broke up after 3 years 11 months. Spent Christmas surfing in El Salvador and Costa Rica while attending Nga and Pete’s 25th anniversary vow renewal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Books Read This Year&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Testament of Hope: Writings and Speeches of Martin Luther King Jr.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Animal Farm, George Orwell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reinventing American Health Care, Ezekiel J. Emanuel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite Songs of 2019&lt;/strong&gt; (not repeating the 2018 ones):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izRqdNeTYbE&quot;&gt;You’ve Got Your Whole Life Ahead Of You, IDER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izRqdNeTYbE&quot;&gt;Sun In our Eyes, MØ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6OFv566mj7s&quot;&gt;Rainbow, Kacey Musgraves&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZ1OGXxb6PM&quot;&gt;Winnebago, Gryffin ft. Quinn XCII, Daniel Wison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LM-BakWpN4k&quot;&gt;Cinnamon Girl, ASL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send Me Off, Bastille. Added this last minute because I played it while writing this. Actually, the entirety of Golden Hour by Kacey Musgraves is good. I also really like the title Space Cowboy since it feels so Cowboy Bebop, even though it isn’t jazz funk. It reminds me of Julia Blues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolutions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I didn’t get as strong as I wanted to, but I did lift more weights in 2019. I think I may try a personal trainer in 2020. But I resolve to be stronger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really enjoyed El Salvador and the hostels in Costa Rica. I will try to travel solo again in 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I miss ultimate frisbee. I will play more. Beach Pickups, here I come!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try to blog more often. My instagram daily posts only worked for 30-odd days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore more of LA. I haven’t been to a concert here!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictions and Politics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2013 I predicted we’d have a half asian woman president for 2020. I’m beginning to think Bernie-Warren with Yang ideas is the best I’m going to get. But I also predicted war starting in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;America’s started the year with assassinations. Let us remember Asimov, “Violence is the last refuge of the incompetent”. Here’s to getting through the year with minimal bloodshed globally.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>